<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Forty</title>
    <link>/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Forty</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CV of Hanna Zimmer</title>
      <link>/projects/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/project2/</guid>
      <description> Short Summary  Currently reading for the Masters in Financial Analysis at London Business School Previously worked in M&amp;amp;A and Private Equity Recently started working with R   Education    Date  Location  Institution  Degree      2020-2022  London, UK  London Business School  MSc in Financial Analysis    2016-2019  Vallendar, GER  WHU - Otto Beisheim School of Management  BSc in International Business Administration    2018  Paris, FR  Essec Business School  Global BBA (Semester Abroad)    2013-2016  Witley, UK  King Edward’s School  International Baccalaureate      Work Experience    Date  Location  Company  Position      2020  Frankfurt, GER  Rothschild &amp;amp; Co  Intern, M&amp;amp;A    2019/2020  Königstein, GER  Silver Investment Partners  Intern, Investment Team    2019  Berlin, GER  Enpal  Intern    2018  Tokyo, JP  Evonik Nippon Aerosil  Intern, Marketing Team    2016  Friedrichsdorf, GER  Pharmalex  Intern, M&amp;amp;A Department      Extra-curricular activities  LBS Women in Business Club IB/PE/AM Lead: Empowering women in Finance through building networks and inspiring the next generation of leaders Member of WHU’s National Model United Nations Club: Participated in conferences in Hamburg and New York with aim of defending a country’s position in a plenum and collaborating with other countries in developing resolutions on aftermath of Syrian civil war and counter-terrorism efforts Workshops &amp;amp; Competitions: Morgan Stanley Future Female Traders Workshop (2020), BCG Case Workshop on Digitalisation and Social Impact (2019) Hobbies: Tennis (14 years), skiing (18 years), reading (recent book: Prisoners of Geography)   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Covid 19 Analysis</title>
      <link>/projects/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/project1/</guid>
      <description>CDC COVID-19 Public Use Data # file contains 11 variables and 3.66m rows and is well over 380Mb. # It will take time to download # URL link to CDC to download data url &amp;lt;- &amp;quot;https://data.cdc.gov/api/views/vbim-akqf/rows.csv?accessType=DOWNLOAD&amp;quot; covid_data &amp;lt;- vroom::vroom(url)%&amp;gt;% # If vroom::vroom(url) doesn&amp;#39;t work, use read_csv(url) clean_names() Given the data we have, I will produce two graphs that show death % rate:
by age group, sex, and whether the patient had co-morbidities or not by age group, sex, and whether the patient was admited to Intensive Care Unit (ICU) or not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/projects/hannacv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/hannacv/</guid>
      <description> Some stuff about me  I poisoned myself doing research. I was the first woman to win a Nobel prize I was the first person and only woman to win a Nobel prize in two different sciences.   Education  Nobel Prizes  Publications 
 </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
